闭嘴
Shut up!
早 你醒了
Hey, you're up.
我昨晚不确定你是否想睡这儿
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you, you know, wanted to... sleep in or not, so...
我在宿舍里？
Am I in a dorm room?
是的
Uh... yeah.
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone ∮
我的衣服呢？
Where are my clothes?
在化妆台上
O-On the dresser.
我昨晚把你的裤子叠起来了
I... folded your pants last night,
- 我不知道它会不会起皱 - 好极了
- and I wasn't sure if that... material gets wrinkled. - Great.
不知道你还记不记得我的名字
don't know if you remember my name or not.
- 昨晚喝大了 - 泰诺？
- Uh, pretty wasted last night. - Got Tylenol?
什么？
What?
我头好痛
My head is killing me.
你有没有泰诺止痛片？
Do you have any Tylenol?
有的
Yes.
当然有
I do.
等等
Uh, sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
顺便说一下 我是卡特
I'm Carter, by the way.
这事对别人保密 懂吗？
Not a word of this to anyone. Got it?
好 没问题
Yeah. Sure.
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or wha...
白痴 来的正好
Nice one, dickhead.
你好
Hey.
抵制全球变暖？
Stop global warming? I...
- 快跑 - 63瓶啤酒在墙上
- Come on! - ∮ On the wall, 63 bottles of beer ∮
63瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ On the wall, 63 bottles of beer... ∮
才坚持了26个小时就不行了？
26 hours, that's all you've got?
一瓶瓶的啤酒在墙上
∮ Bottles of beer on the wall ∮
- 大点声 - 62瓶啤酒在墙上
- I can't hear you! - ∮ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
62瓶啤酒
∮ 62 bottles of beer ∮
你取下一瓶 传给下一个
∮ You take one down, pass it around ∮
- 别停 - 61瓶啤酒在墙上
- Keep going! - ∮ 61 bottles of beer on the wall... ∮
嗨
Hey.
你好
Hi.
我发的短信你一条都没回
You haven't... returned any of my texts.
是啊 抱歉我很忙
Yeah. Sorry, I've been busy.
是啊 显而易见
Yeah. I can see that.
听着 蒂姆 我们是约会过
Okay, Tim, we went on a date.
只有一次
One.
我没必要回你短信
I don't have to text you back.
我们什么也不算
We're not, like, a thing.
好吧
Okay. I just...
我以为我们相处得很愉快
you know, I figured we had a nice time...
你很愉快
You had a nice time.
我很悲惨
I was miserable.
谁会带女孩去赛百味约会？
I mean, who takes their first date to Subway?
你还没他们家的三明治长
It's not like you have a footlong.
你觉得看起来像是感染吗？
Does this look infected to you?
有人喝了我的康普茶
Someone drank my kombucha.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God.
你这个鬼鬼祟祟的小婊砸
You sneaky little beyatch.
那人是谁？
Who was it?
不是谁
Nobody.
姐妹之间没有秘密
Sisters don't keep secrets.
- 说真的 那人真的谁也不是 - 好吧
- Seriously, it was nobody. - Well,
我希望"谁也不是"做了保护措施
I hope "nobody" used a condom.
- 我们可不想谁看起来像个荡妇 - 丹妮尔 谢谢关心
- We don't want "somebody" looking like a whore. - Thanks, Danielle, super helpful.
谁叫我们是姐妹呢？
What are sisters for? Oh.
- 别忘了午饭时有宿舍例会 - 死都忘不了
- And don't forget, house meeting at lunch. - Living for it.
你可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
我昨晚是不是特丢人？
Did I totally embarrass myself last night?
才没有呢
Not at all.
除了在桌子上跳舞 和人打了两架
Unless you consider dancing on a table, starting two fights,
把椒盐脆饼块吐得到处都是之外
and barfing pretzel chunks all over the bar embarrassing.
快告诉我这都不是真的
Please tell me you're kidding.
对了 你还把舌头伸到尼克·西姆斯的嗓子眼里
Oh, and you also rammed your tongue down Nick Sims' throat
当着丹妮尔的面
right in front of Danielle.
天啊
Oh, God,
她今天早上还关心我来着
but she was so nice to me this morning.
是啊 她和你一样昨晚喝大了
Yeah, I think she was as drunk as you last night,
把这当成集体失忆症吧
so consider it collective amnesia.
谢谢老天
Oh, thank God for that.
糟糕 我上课晚了
Oh... crap, I'm so late for class.
找不到我的书了
Can't find my damn book.
别以为你骗得了我？
Did you really think you could keep it a secret from me?
- 你怎么发现的？- 你驾照上有出生日期
- How did you find out? - Driver's license.
我只能说照片还行
Not the best picture, I might add.
- 我猜你把我来电铃声也改了 - 谁改的 我吗？
- I assume you changed my ringer, too. - Who, me?
没有的事
Never.
你许了什么愿？
What'd you wish for?
- 想要个新室友 - 傻瓜
- A new roommate. - Wench.
那可是我亲手做的
Uh... I made that from scratch.
抱歉 太多碳水化合物了 拜拜
Sorry. Too many carbs. Toodles.
题目中的机能反应表现了…
Locomotive response in the subject shows an acceleration
量子平面的加速
across the quantum plane.
它导致了部分正价的β碳原子和部分负价的氢碱基
This creates great orbital overlap between the partially positive beta carbon...
在轨道上重叠
and the partially negative hydrogen alkali group.
谢谢
Thanks.
大赛临近 弘扬校风
Get your school spirit on before the big game.
学生证打九折
Ten percent off with your student ID.
还要挑选今年的慈善项目
And we still need to pick this year's charity.
我现在宣布 我们不能再举办特殊人士艺术集会了
I can say right now, there's no way we're doing the Special Needs Art Fair again.
吓坏我了 你们说呢？
Totally freaked my shit out. Thoughts.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.
怎么了 小翠？
What's wrong, Tree?
没什么 除了看到你在我们的桌子上丢下的猫女郎自助餐
Nothing. Except for that cat lady buffet you just dumped at our table.
我是看到巧克力牛奶了吗？
And is that chocolate milk I see?
我还没吃早餐了
I missed breakfast.
早餐是什么 贝基？
What is breakfast, Becky?
- 我很抱歉 - 混蛋
- Oh! I'm sorry. - Oh, asshole!
- 我很抱歉 小翠 - 等等
- I'm sorry, Tree. - Wait,
你们俩认识？
you two know each other?
- 是的 - 才不呢
- Yeah, I... - No.
我们去年一起上过课
We had a... a class together last year.
看 我是来拿给你这个的
Look, I was... bringing you this back.
抱歉 我不知道你住哪儿
Sorry, I didn't know where you lived, you know?
我…
I...
抱歉给你添麻烦了
I'm sorry again about the... the mess.
人渣
What a douchebag.
劳伦斯医生请到门诊部来
Dr. Lawrence to outpatient services.
耶 今天是我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone ∮
- 洛丽 - 嗨
- Lori. - Hi.
嗨
Hi.
我以为你只上晚班
Um... so, I thought you only worked nights.
我替珍代班 她得了流感
Doing a double for Jen. She has the flu.
- 你人真好 - 我猜我不用问你来这里做什么
- That's nice of you. - So, I guess I don't need to ask what you're doing here.
得赶紧走了
Gotta go.
听好 小翠
Look, Tree...
虽然这不关我事
it's none of my business,
但我觉得你这么做
but... I think something like this
会留下严重后果的
is bound to have some pretty serious consequences.
你说的对
You're right.
这不关你事
It is none of your business.
希尔德医生和玛格兰医生 请到2476病房
Dr. Surd and Dr. Margolan, 2476.
今天不能陪你了 医院里事情太多了
We can't do this today... there's too much going on in the building.
我还有别人
I have patients.
我就是你的病人
And I'm losing mine.
格里高利？
Gregory?
- 嘿 - 嘿 亲爱的
- Hey. - Hey, sweetie.
门怎么了？
What's with the door?
有东西堵住了 我们刚结束
Oh, stupid thing got jammed. Oh, just wrapping up here.
见过我学生特蕾莎吗？
Have you met my student, Teresa?
不 我没见过
No. I haven't.
你好 幸会
Hi. It's nice to meet you.
谢谢你帮我
Thank you so much for helping me out.
你来真让我惊喜
This is a nice surprise.
自从我们上次大吵一架后 内森就变得很冷淡
Nathan's been acting really strange since our big fight,
今天早上 他开车去亚特兰大
and this morning he drove to Atlanta
- 去参加关于新体育馆开业的紧急会议 - 进来
- for a last-minute business meeting about opening a new gym. - Enter.
我感觉很奇怪 因为我从没听说过这件事
Which is weird, because I've never heard anything about it before.
我试着不让这件事困扰我
But I'm trying not to let that bring me down.
- 你穿的是我的上衣吗？- 我穿着好不好看？
- Is that my top? - How cute is it on me?
随便吧 拜托别弄脏了就行
Whatever. Just don't get anything on it, please.
你意思是别让尼克的奶油饼干弄脏？
You mean like Nick's Nutter Butter?
哇 他很厉害吗 丹妮尔？
Wow. How's he, Danielle?
今晚你几点来派对？
What time you going to the party tonight?
我不知道 一会儿吧
I don't know. Later.
咱的学费算是白交了
Our tuition dollars at work.
无论如何
Anyhoo...
别来太晚 不然Σ兄弟会的小鲜肉就被抢走了
don't be too late, or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
好的 拜拜
Okay. Bye-ee.
- 拜拜 - 谁拿了我的吹风机？
- Bye-ee. - Who took my hairdryer?
疯婆子
Crazy bitch.
特蕾莎 我是爸爸
Teresa, it's Dad.
我在餐厅等了你一个多小时
I sat in that restaurant waiting for you for over an hour.
真不敢相信你这么对我
I can't believe you would do this to me,
偏偏是今天
today of all days.
好吧 你们真会玩
Okay, you guys are hilarious.
别躲了 出来吧
You can come out now.
胆小鬼
Losers.
喂 你的朋友从另一边走了
Yo, I think your friends went the other way.
你有什么事吗？
Can I help you?
听着 怪人
Look, weirdo,
我才不怕你呢 你怎么不去吓唬吓唬Δ姐妹会的小母狗们？
I'm not scared. Why don't you go try this with one of the heifers at Delta Gamma?
她们喜欢角色扮演
They're into cosplay.
我要叫警察了
Okay, I'm calling the cops.
闭嘴
Shut up!
早 你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我昨晚不确定你是否想睡这儿
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you, you know, wanted to sleep in or not, so...
对 是
Right. Yeah.
我昨晚把你的裤子叠起来了
I folded your pants... for you last night,
我不知道它会不会起皱
and I wasn't sure if... the material gets... wrinkled.
不知道你还记不记得我的名字
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
你昨晚喝大了
You know, you were... pretty wasted last night.
但…
But, uh...
- 我是… 我是… - 卡特
- I'm... I'm... - Carter.
你竟然记得
You remembered.
- 啊 泰诺？- 什么？
- Uh, Tylenol? - What?
我头好痛 你有没有泰诺止痛片？
Oh, my head is killing me... do you have any Tylenol?
有的
Oh, uh... yes.
在那边
It's over there.
对
Right.
在你的衣服下面
It's under your clothes, on... on the...
- 对 - 是的 是的
- Okay. - Right. Right.
谢谢
Ah, thanks.
好像你以前来过一样
It's like you've been here before.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
小翠？
Tree?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or wha...
抱歉
I'm... I'm sorry.
白痴 来的正好
Nice one, dickhead.
你好
Hey.
抵制全球变暖？
Stop global warming? I...
抱歉 不了
Um, sorry, no, thanks.
快跑
Come on!
64瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ 64 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
- 拜托 我湿透了 - 64瓶啤酒
- Please! I'm soaked! - ∮ 64 bottles of beer ∮
你取下一瓶 传给下一个 63瓶啤酒
∮ You take one down, pass it around, 63 bottles of beer ∮
63瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ On the wall, 63 bottles of beer... ∮
- 才坚持了26个小时就不行了？-  63瓶啤酒
- 26 hours, that's all you've got? - ∮ 63 bottles of beer ∮
- 继续 - 62瓶啤酒在墙上
- Keep going! - ∮ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
- 快点 - 62瓶啤酒在墙上
- Faster! - ∮ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
62瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ 62 bottles of beer ∮
- 继续 - 你取下一瓶
- Keep going! - ∮ You take one down ∮
- 大声点 - 传给下一个
- I can't hear you! - ∮ Pass it around ∮
61瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ 61 bottles of beer on the wall... ∮
嗨
Hey.
我发的短信你一条都没回
You... haven't returned any of my texts.
蒂姆 今天几号？
Tim, what day is it?
18号星期一
Uh... Monday the 18th.
你确定
You're sure?
我十分确定
I'm pretty sure.
我…
I, um...
我得走了
I gotta go.
打给我？
Call me?
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God.
你这个鬼鬼祟祟的小婊砸
You sneaky little beyatch.
那人是谁？
Who was it?
姐妹之间没有秘密
Sisters don't keep secrets.
- 我现在感觉一切都似曾相识 - 噢
- I'm totally having déjà vu right now. - Oh.
哦 我一直这么觉得 这意味着
I have it all the time. It's supposed to mean, like,
某些人在打飞机的时候想着你
someone's thinking about you while they're masturbating.
我一天有五次这种感觉
I have it at least five times a day.
说真的 我一整天都这样 太奇怪了
Seriously, I've been having it all day, it's so weird.
也许下次你应该多喝点水 亲
Maybe you should switch to water next time, hon.
好的 谢啦 我会记住的
Uh, yeah, thanks. I'll keep that in mind.
谁叫我们是姐妹呢？噢 别忘了
What are sisters for? Oh! And don't forget,
午饭时有宿舍例会
house meeting at lunch.
听见了吗？
Hello?
上周四就通知了 小翠
It's been on the board since last Thursday, Tree.
好 我记住了
Yeah, I remember. I...
你可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
太奇怪了
That's so weird.
你还好吗？
You okay?
你昨晚喝大了
You were kind of a mess last night.
糟糕 我上课晚了
Oh, shit, I'm so late for class.
别以为你骗得了我？
Did you really think you could keep it a secret from me?
不想知道我是怎么发现的吗？
Don't you want to know how I found out?
你看我驾照了？
Driver's license?
真聪明
Clever girl.
不过你的证件照 呵呵？
That picture, though?
我得走了
I got to go.
但…
But...
可你还没吹…
you-you didn't even blow out the...
蜡烛
...candle.
我们必须在Σ派对上增加博弈
We really need to step up our game at these frat parties, okay?
还要挑选今年的的慈善项目
And... we still need to pick this year's charity.
我现在宣布 我们不能再举办特殊人士艺术集会了
I can say right now there's no way we're doing the Special Needs Art Fair again.
大赛临近 弘扬校风
Get your school spirit on before the big game.
学生证打九折
Ten percent off with your student ID.
T恤
T-shirts.
怎么了 小翠？
What's wrong, Tree?
我猜我只是有点累了
Um, I'm just a little tired I guess.
不 混蛋
No, dumbass.
到底怎么回事？
What's wrong with that?
太不像你风格了
So not Kappa cuisine.
我是不是看到了巧克力牛奶？
And is that chocolate milk I see?
我还没吃早餐了
I missed breakfast.
我们都不吃早餐 贝基
We all miss breakfast, Becky.
贝基
Becky.
贝基 小心
Becky, look out.
- 我很抱歉 小翠 - 等等
- I'm... so sorry. I'm sorry, Tree. - Wait.
你们俩认识？
You two know each other?
- 是的 - 才不呢
- No. - Yeah. I mean...
我们去年一起上过课
we had a... a class together last year.
仅此而已
That's all.
抱歉给你添麻烦了
I'm sorry about all this.
等等
Hey.
怎么了？
What?
我的手镯
My bracelet.
再次抱歉给你添麻烦了
You know, I'm sorry again about... you know, the mess.
人渣
What a douchebag.
今天不能陪你了
Hey, we can't do this today.
医院里事情太多了
There's too much going on in the building.
我有话跟你说
I need to talk to you.
小翠 我..
Tree, I...
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
你知道？
You do?
听着 年轻女孩喜欢上老男人很正常
Look, it's normal for a young girl to have feelings for an older man,
但你不能动真感情
but you can't fall in love.
我没动真感情
I'm not falling in love with you.
你没有吗？
You're not?
没有 只是今天很奇怪
No. I've been having the weirdest day and... mmm.
你老婆
Your wife.
真扫兴
Uh, that's kind of a buzzkill.
格里高利
Gregory.
你在里面吗？
Are you in there?
多谢你锁了门
Thank God you locked the door.
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
我没注意到我锁了门
Uh, I didn't realize I'd locked the door, um...
我们刚结束
uh, just wrapping up here.
见过我学生特蕾莎吗？
Have you met my student, Teresa?
不
No.
我没见过
I haven't.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
祝我们生日快乐
∮ Happy birthday to us ∮
∮ Happy birthday to us. ∮
我最爱的女孩们 吹灭它
My favorite girls. Blow it out.
真棒
There you go.
- 爸 怎么了？- 来人啊
- Dad, what's up? - You guys,
我找到一只小虫子
I think I just spotted a bug.
- 哪里？- 就在这儿 看到了吗？细看看
- Where? - Right there. See? Take a look. Mm-hmm.
- 妈妈… - 妈妈出招了
- Mom... - And Mom goes in for the kill!
- 噢 天啊 - 噢 好惨
- Oh, my God! - Oh, no.
别看我
Don't look at me.
看来我没剩饭了
Oh, I guess I'm not having leftovers.
- 参加关于新体育馆开业的紧急会议 - 好啦
- ...last minute business meeting about opening new gym. - I know.
我只借穿一晚上
I'm just borrowing it for tonight.
晚上你几点来派对？
What time you going to the party?
我试着不让这件事困扰我
...to let that bring me down, because...
你在听吗？
Hello?
- 走神的婊子 - 什么？
- Earth to space bitch. - What?
今晚你几点来派对？
What time are you going to the party?
我不知道 一会儿吧
Uh, f... I don't know. Later.
咱的学费算是白交了
Our tuition dollars at work.
好的 哇
Okay, whoa.
亲 别怕 不过又是短路
Chill out. It's just another rolling blackout, sweetie.
- 这事发生过？- 是呀
- It happened before? - Yeah.
两周前吧
Like, two weeks ago.
无论如何 别来太晚
Anyhoo... don't be too late
不然Σ兄弟会的小鲜肉就被抢走了
or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
谁拿了我的吹风机？
Who took my hairdryer?
特蕾莎 我是爸爸
Teresa, it's Dad.
我在餐厅等了你一个多小时
I sat in that restaurant waiting for you for over an...
麦克
Yo, Mike.
快点 追上来
Come on, hurry up, man.
稍等 这就来
Hold up. I'm coming.
赶上了
Here we come!
不会吧
No way.
惊喜？
Surprise?
你太狠了 小翠？
What the hell, Tree?
哦 天啊 对不起
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
我以为你
I thought that you...
真抱歉
I am so, so sorry. I...
别惹咱们的Κ妞儿
Don't mess with a Kappa bitch.
- 你说真的吗？- 是的
- Are you serious? - Yes.
那个贱人
That slut.
- 谁？- 洛丽
- Who? - Lori.
她说她会来
She said she'd be here.
她明年别想跟我们一起住
She's so out of the house next year.
我记得她说要值两轮班
I think she said she had, like, a double shift.
随便她 她和一些神秘人混在一起
Whatevs. She's been boning some mystery guy.
那是你的跟踪狂
There's your stalker.
他身材真棒
He's so hot.
- 丹妮尔 - 怎么？
- Danielle! - What?
太恶心了吧
That is so gross.
好吧
Oh, okay.
停战？
Cheers?
嗨
Hi.
为什么你要戴那只愚蠢的面具？
Why were you wearing that stupid mask anyway?
周五有好戏了
The big game's on Friday,
我只是想展示校风
I just thought I'd show a little school spirit.
没想到因此被打了
Never thought I'd get clocked for it.
我很抱歉 你冰敷了么？
I really am sorry. Did you ice it?
还好
It's fine.
你可以过一会儿补偿我
You can make it up to me later.
怎么？
What?
不要敷衍我
Don't "what" me.
小翠 你知道自己在做什么
You know exactly what you're doing, Tree.
我怎么了 丹妮尔？
What am I doing, Danielle?
丹妮尔？
Danielle.
尼克？
Nick?
哇
Wow.
尼克 讨厌 你吓到我了
Oh, shit, Nick, you scared me.
你想让我再往你脸上打一拳吗？
You want me to punch you in the face again?
欢迎来到…
Welcome...
欢乐谷
to the Pleasure Dome.
你不觉得有点吵吗？
It's a little loud, don't you think?
好吧
Okay!
我真的受够了
I'm officially over this.
你自己在撒哈拉帐篷里玩吧
Have fun in the Sahara Tent.
听好 尼克 说真的
Come on, Nick, seriously,
丹妮尔气坏了
Danielle's, like, freaking out.
不要
Oh!
救命 救命
Help me! Help me!
混蛋
You asshole!
不
No!
你还好吧？
What, is everything okay?
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. ∮
怎么…
What's...
不知道你还记不记得我的名字
I mean, I don't know if you remember my name or not.
- 你昨晚… - 喝大了
- You were... - Pretty wasted?
没错
Yeah.
- 你叫卡特？- 没错
- And your name's Carter. - Yeah.
我们之前见过吗？
And we've never met before.
昨晚之前没有
I mean, no, not until last night.
哦 天啊 真是一场噩梦
Oh, my God, this is a nightmare.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
请你搞清楚 是你想要和我回来的
You were the one that wanted to come home with me.
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that fine vagi...
白痴 来的正好
Nice one, dickhead.
抵制全球变暖？
Stop global warming?
说"不用"就好了
A simple "no thanks" would do!
才坚持了26个小时就不行了？
26 hours, that's all you got?
别停
Keep going!
62瓶啤酒...
∮ 62 bottles of beer... ∮
大点声
I can't hear you!
嗨
Hey.
你还好吗？
You okay?
我发的短信你一条都没回
You haven't returned any of my texts.
你可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
你还好吗？
Hey, you okay?
小翠？
Tree?
小翠 怎么了？
Tree, what's wrong?
说话啊
Say something.
洛丽 我..
Lori, I...
我感觉我疯了
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what's happening to me.
别怕
Okay.
冷静点
Just calm down.
告诉我发生了什么？
Tell me what's going on.
听着 我知道这难以置信
Look, I know this isn't gonna make any sense,
但是我已经过完今天了
but I have already lived through this day.
两次
Twice.
- 小翠 我… - 不 不 不
- Tree, I, um... - No, no, no,
相信我 我知道这听起来不正常
believe me, I know it sounds totally crazy,
但我向天发誓 这是真的
but this is happening to me, I swear to God.
小翠 我相信你感觉像经历过
Tree, I'm sure it feels like you're living through...
好吧 你做了纸杯蛋糕
O-Okay, okay, you made me a cupcake.
为了我的生日 对吗？
For my birthday, right?
你准备要给我 今晚也会有个惊喜派对
You're about to give it to me and then later on tonight,there's a surprise party.
谁告诉你的？
Who told you?
- 贝基？- 不 不 没人告诉我
- Was it Becky? - No, no, nobody told me.
我说我过完今天了 你看不出来吗？
That's what I mean. Don't you see?
我知道会发生什么
I know what is going to happen before it happens.
- 只是… - 洛丽
- Just... - Lori.
洛丽 有人今晚要杀我
Lori, somebody's gonna kill me tonight.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 我懂了
Okay, I get it.
谁让你设计我的？
Who put you up to this?
- 是丹妮尔吗？- 不 不
- Was it Danielle? - No, no,
不 这不是玩笑话
no, this isn't some stupid joke.
是真实发生的
This is actually happening to me.
我不知是谁要杀我
I don't know who's going to kill me,
但是有人会杀了我
but someone is, I just don't know who it is yet.
- 我… - 小翠 你吓到我了
- I... - Tree, you're starting to freak me out.
你以为我不害怕吗？
Well, how do you think I feel?
小翠 看着我
Tree, look at me.
没人要杀你
Nobody is trying to kill you.
- 不 他们会的 洛丽 - 小翠 看着我
- Yes, they are, Lori. - Tree, look at me.
我知道今天对你母亲和所有人来说都很难过
I know that today's hard with your mom and all.
为什么你不翘课呢？
Why don't you skip class?
请假休息一天
Just... take the day off and get some rest.
我保证你明天就好了
I promise you, you'll feel better tomorrow.
好吗？
Okay?
混蛋 看看你还进的来么
Let's see you get in here now, asshole.
小翠？
Tree?
怎么把门给锁了？
Why is the door locked?
我需要点时间独处
Um, I-I just need some alone time.
今晚你几点来派对？
What time you going to the party tonight?
我不知道
I don't know.
咱的学费算是白交了
Our tuition dollars at work.
无论如何
Anyhoo...
别来太晚 不然Σ兄弟会的小鲜肉就被抢走了
don't be too late or all the cute Sigma boys will be taken.
好的 拜拜
Okay, see you soon.
谁拿了我的吹风机？
Who took my hairdryer?
新体育馆开业
...opening a new gym.
我感觉很奇怪 因为我从没听说过这件事
Which is weird, because I've never heard anything about it before.
我试着不让这件事困扰我
But I'm trying not to let that bring me down,
因为我在去接小贾的路上
because I'm on my way to pick up Jace.
太好了
I'm just happy
你要见到小贾了
you're gonna see Jace this morning.
- 是呀 - 已经一个多月了
- I know. - It's been, like, almost a month.
他见到你会很开心的
He's gonna be so excited to see you.
洛丽把遥控器放哪儿了？
Where'd Lori put the fricking remote?
- 你好 小贾 - 你好 小贾
- Hi, Jace! - Hey, Jace!
你好呀
Hey!
(今天是你生日)
我是芭芭拉
I'm Barbara.
- 我是克里斯托 - 你好
- I am Crystal. - Hi.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
(生日快乐 又长大一岁)
- 和妈妈说再见好吗？- 拜
- Can you say bye to Mamey? - Bye.
乖乖的 好好玩…
Stay buckled and have a good time...
G-48
G-48!
好棒呀
Aingt that great!
- G-48 - G-48
- G-48! - G-48!
我不知道你和那个男的怎么回事
I don't know what's going on with you and that other guy, okay?
因枪伤被送去抢救
is being treated for a gunshot wound
在今早的致命枪击后
following a deadly shootout this morning
导致一名警察殉职
that left one officer dead.
塘卜司是作为…
Tombs was the subject of...
发型没新意？
Do you go through a can of hairspray
你是否为了秀发浓密 遍寻喷发剂无果？
trying to get that full, volumized look?
用邦佩特轻松一喷
Then bump it up with Bumpits...
就能达到专业美发效果
...and get that salon-style look,
完美发型 轻松见效
flat to fabulous, instantly.
想象创造了今天的…
Imagine being able to create today's hottest...
噢 天啊 噢 天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
噢 天啊…
Oh, my...
怎么了？
What's wrong?
What's going on?
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta... ∮
- 噢 - 小翠 你还好吗？你生病了吗？
- Ow. - Tree? Are you okay? Are you sick?
- 闭嘴 闭嘴 闭嘴 - 耶 今天我生日
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! - ∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
- 闭嘴 - 赶快接电话
- Shut up! - ∮ And I ain't gotta... ∮
老天 停下来吧
Oh, my God, make it stop,
- 停下来 停下来 - 你还好吗？
- make it stop, make it stop. - Are you okay?
- 离我远点 - 好吧
- Get away from me! - All right.
冷静 你…
Come on, just...
你取下一瓶 传给下一个
∮ You take one down, pass it around ∮
- 大点声 - 61瓶啤酒在墙上
- Louder! - ∮ 61 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
61瓶啤酒在墙上
∮ 61 bottles of beer on the wall ∮
- 大点声 - 你取下一瓶 传给下一个
- I can't hear you! - ∮ You take one down, pass it around ∮
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你忘了你的东西
You... forgot your stuff.
你取下一瓶 传给下一个
∮ You take one down, pass it around ∮
- 帮我 - 60瓶啤酒在墙上
- Help me. - ∮ 60 bottles of beer on the wall... ∮
能别这么看着我吗
Will you please stop staring at me
好像我脸上有东西
like I took a dump on your mom's head?
不好意思 我只是在整理思路
I'm sorry. I'm... just trying to... wrap my brain around this.
你是怎么想的？
How's that going for you?
假设如果你说的有一丝丝可能的话
Assuming that I believe any of this is even remotely possible,
你被困在今天一定是有原因的？
there has to be a reason you're stuck in this day, okay?
在你的一生里
Out of all the days of your life,
是什么让今天变得特别？
what makes this day special?
是什么让它有意义？
What gives this day meaning?
- 什么也不是 - 耶 今天我生日
- Nothing. - ∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. ∮
你今天过生日？
It's your birthday?
是的
Yeah.
- 你好？- 生日不过就是
- Hello? - So? Birthdays are just excuses
吃蛋糕 拆礼物和放纵自己的借口
to, like, eat cake and open presents and shit.
生日本身毫无意义
There's no real meaning behind a birthday.
不 它是一个指示 懂吗？
No, it's symbolic, okay?
谁会在你生日的时候杀了你
Whoever's killing you knows it's your birthday.
好吧 听着
All right, look.
给我一张知道你生日的人的名单
Give me a list of names of everybody who knows it's your birthday
以及想要杀你的人的名单
and whoever's trying to kill you.
多亏了姐妹会 几乎全校都知道今天我过生日
Well, thanks to my sorority, pretty much the entire school knows it's my birthday.
她们今晚要给我办惊喜派对
They're throwing me this stupid surprise party tonight.
真的谁都可能杀了我
I mean, it literally could be anyone.
谁有动机呢？
I mean, who has motive?
好吧 可能是丹妮尔
Okay, maybe it's Danielle.
- 好的 - 显然 我当着她的面和她喜欢的男生亲热
- All right. - Apparently, I made out with some guy she liked right in front of her last night.
这一定是我们见面以前
Oh. Must have been before we met.
你晚上很忙么？
Busy night?
好吧 "捡尸体"先生
Okay, Mr. I'm Gonna Take This Drunk Girl Home
不要对我评头论足
and Take Advantage of Her, don't judge.
我必须纠正一下 我昨晚没占你便宜 好吗？
For the record, I didn't take advantage of you last night.
我在瑞恩床上睡的
Okay? I slept on Ryan's bed.
所以 我们没有…
So, w... we didn't...
- 做过… - 没
- have s... - No.
你昨晚喝大了
You were wasted last night.
我只是担心你像詹尼斯·乔普林一样被自己的呕吐物呛死
And I was afraid you were gonna fall or choke on your own vomit, like Janis Joplin.
我们说到哪儿了？
Uh, wh... what were we...
- 嫌疑人 - 对 嫌疑人
- Suspects. - Right, suspects.
好吧 丹妮尔
Um, okay, so Danielle.
格里高利
There's... Gregory.
他的老婆
Um, his wife.
跟踪狂蒂姆
Creepy Tim.
把我从TJ Maxx开除的小个子女孩
Oh. Um, that tiny girl from T.J. Maxx that I got fired.
还有上周被我吐唾沫的优步司机
And maybe the Uber driver that I spit on last week.
我记得他叫…
I think his name was...
怎么？人无完人
What? Nobody's perfect.
好吧 这没什么用
Okay, this isn't helping.
这没什么用 不是吗？
This is pointless, isn't it?
好吧 听着 在我看来…
All right, look, the way I see it is-is...
你有了无限的生命
you have unlimited amount of lives,
所以你有无限的机会
so you have unlimited opportunities to solve
- 去抓到杀你的人 - 你的意思是
- your own murder. - So I'm just supposed to keep dying
我在找到杀人犯之前就一遍一遍地死去？
until I figure out who my killer is?
- 这就是你出的好主意？- 你有更好的办法吗？
- That's your genius plan? - Do you have a better idea?
蒂姆 你出来一下？
Yo, Tim! You coming out?
嘿
Hey!
太累了
It's so exhausting.
混蛋
Asshole!
- 你个贱人 - 噢
- You bitch! - Ow!
我就知道是你
I knew it was you!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
噢 天啊 贝基？
Oh, my God. Becky?
贝基
Becky.
贝基 贝基？
Becky! Becky?
- 闭嘴 - 噢
- Shut up! - Ow.
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday, and I ain't ∮
- 早 你醒了 - 赶快接电话
- Oh, hey. You're up. - ∮ Gotta pick up the phone... ∮
我昨晚不确定你是否想睡这儿
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you wanted to... sleep in or not.
你的主意糟透了
Your plan totally sucks.
什么？
What?
不知道你还记不记得我的名字
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
你昨晚喝大了
You know, you were... pretty wasted last night.
我是卡特
Um... but I'm Carter.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
不能更好了
Never better.
- 你确定你还好吗？- 我很好
- Are you sure you're okay? - Yeah, I'm-I'm fine.
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or wha...
怎么了
'Sup? Hey, um...
对不起 打扰了
I'm sorry to bother you guys, uh...
卡特
Uh... Carter?
拜托 帮帮我 卡特？
Please? A little help? Carter?
小翠
Tree.
冷静
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down.
是我
It's-it's just me.
你还好吗
How you doing?
怎么了？
What... what happened?
你今天早上晕倒了
You... you collapsed this morning.
今天是哪天？
What day is it?
星期一
Uh, it's Monday.
日期？
What's the date?
呃 18号
Uh, it's... the 18th.
我们尝试联系你父母
Oh, we've been trying to get in contact with your parents,
但因为一些原因…
but for some reason...
- 吓我一跳 - 有事吗？
- Geez! - Can I help you?
我…
Uh, I'm just...
- 我就是来看看她 - 没关系的
- I'm checking on her. - It's okay.
- 他是我朋友 - 抱歉 探视时间到
- He's a friend. - Sorry. Visiting hours are over.
好吧
Got it.
谢谢你 卡特
Thanks, Carter.
早日康复
Feel better.
我什么时候能出院？
When can I get out of here?
你的病历真让我为难
Uh, I'm having a hard time pulling your medical records.
为什么？
Why?
这是刚从影像科拿到的
We just got these back from imaging,
这些重大外伤的标记
and these are signs of... major trauma.
标明了疤痕组织和损害面积的严重程度
I mean, given the severity of the scar tissue and the size of the lesions...
这听起来很奇怪 但…
This is gonna sound crazy, but...
你应该已经死了
technically... you should be dead.
等等 你在做什么？
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey. What are you doing?
- 我得离开这儿 - 不行
- I need to get out of here. - No way.
你要留院观察
No, you need to stay here for observation.
如果不离开 我会死
If I don't get out of here, I'm gonna die.
- 我要离开… - 小翠 小翠 嘘 嘘
- I need to go... - Tree, Tree, shh, shh.
听我说
Listen to me.
你在这里绝对安全
You are absolutely safe here.
好的
Okay.
我会保护你
I won't let anything happen to you.
我真的很渴
I'm really thirsty.
能给我杯汽水？
Could you get me a soda?
没问题
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的小快递
Special delivery.
钥匙…
Keys, keys, keys.
妈的
Shit.
格里高利 你的车钥匙在哪里 快出现
Oh, Gregory, where are the car keys? Come on.
小翠 小翠 别怕
Tree, Tree, it's okay.
别怕 是我
It's okay. It's just me.
格里高利 小心
Gregory, look out!
不
No.
No!
天啊 快点
Oh, my God. Come on.
快点
Come on, no.
不
No.
我做到了
I did it.
I did it!
我做到了
太好了
Yeah!
追上我试试 婊子
Catch me now, bitch!
怎么？
What?
天啊 不 不 不….
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
快点
Come on!
不要
No!
惨了
Oh, sh... shit!
惨了 惨了 惨了
Shit, shit, shit.
警官 我知道我超速了
I know I was speeding, Officer.
- 我只是… - 请关闭引擎
- I just... - Turn off the engine, please.
是的 警官
Yes, Officer.
驾照和车辆注册证
License and registration.
我…
I, um...
我没带
I don't have it.
你说什么？
Pardon me?
他还要再杀我一次
He's trying to kill me again.
- 再一次？- 是的
- Again? - Yes.
我的意思是…
I mean, no, I me...
他以前想杀我 但这次我跑掉了
he was trying before, but this time I got away
可我没空拿衣服了
But I-I-I didn't have time to grab my clothes
我的驾照在口袋里
and my driver's license is in my pocket.
女士 你是嗑药或者喝酒了？
Ma'am, are you under the influence of alcohol or any other controlled substance?
没有 我只是想…
No! That is what I'm trying to...
等等
Wait.
如果是 你是不是打算逮捕我
If I am, does that mean that you're going to arrest me
把我锁进监狱里？
and lock me in a jail cell?
按照程序是这样的
That's how it usually works.
我喝多了
I'm drunk.
真的吗？
You are?
喝大了 我不清醒
Wasted. And I'm high.
药丸 大麻
You know, pills, weed.
我什么都吸
You name it, man, I'm on it.
那么…
Uh, well...
既然如此 我只能逮捕你了
then I'm gonna put you under arrest.
好主意
That's a good idea.
让我帮你
Let me help you.
好的
Um, all right.
我还是第一次被抓
You know, never been arrested before.
- 谢谢 - 各单位注意
- Thank you! - All units,
大学医院有情况
we got a 187 at University Hospital.
嫌疑人在逃…
Suspect is believed...
不
No!
天啊 让我出去
Shit. Oh, God, get me out!
让我出去 让我出去
Get me out, get me out!
你想干什么？
What do you want?!
为什么这么对我？
Why are you doing this to me?!
你是谁？
Who are you?
胆小鬼 露出你的脸
Show your face, you pussy!
你要去哪儿？
Where are you going?!
该死
Oh, shit!
我完了
Oh, fuck.
嗨
Oh, hey.
- 你醒了 - 别说话
- You're up. - Silence!
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. ∮
稍等 你以前来过这儿？
Wait, you been here before?
我觉得你最好别吃太多 那样你可能…
Hey, uh, you know, I don't think you should be taking that many. I mean, you could...
你会死的
you could die.
要是那么容易就好了
If only it were that easy.
水 劳驾
Water, por favor.
快点
Come on.
- 给你 - 嗯
- Here you go. - Mm.
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that...
你好
Hi.
我就是你说的"那妞儿"
I'm the so-called fine vagine.
如果你打算一直这么称呼女孩
And if that's the way that you refer to girls,
你以后就一直和自己的手过吧
you and your hand are going to have a very lasting relationship.
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
怎样？
What?
你早上都这么迷人吗？
I mean, are you... you always this charming in the morning?
只有今天早上
Mm. Just this one.
你做什么噩梦了吗？
So were you having a bad dream or something?
噩梦？
Sorry?
你刚才尖叫着醒来
You were just... screaming before you woke up.
我那时快死了
I was dying.
又一次
Again.
什么？
What?
说来话长
Uh, it's a long story.
没事 我有时间
Well, I mean, I-I've got, you know, time.
如果你想说 我乐意奉陪…
I'm not doing anything today, if-if you want to...
说真的？
Seriously?
我讨厌这张贴纸
I hate this sticker.
等一下
Hey, wait!
你为什么跟着我？
Why are you following me?
我想听你讲你的故事
I... I want to hear your story.
听着 没有冒犯的意思 但上次
Look, no offense, but the last time
我跟你说的时候 并没有什么卵用
I explained it to you, it got me nowhere.
所以…
So...
上一次？
"The last time"?
等等
Hey.
你真的做噩梦了
So you're-you're having bad dreams.
- 我有上过神经认知和梦境的选修课 - 确实可以帮助你吹嘘
- I took an elective course on neurocognition in dream content. - Mm. Hooray for you.
我的意思是…
I'm just saying, I-I...
我也许能帮到你
I might be able to help, you know?
你能帮我解决日复一日
Can you help me stop reliving the same day over and over,
被认识或不认识的人在同一天杀死又活过来吗？
only to be murdered by someone I may or may not know?
是的 我觉得可以
Yeah. Thought so.
- 抵制全球变暖？- 嗯
- Stop global warming? - Mm.
等等 你真的觉得自己每天都过的一样吗？
So, wait, you literally think you're reliving the same day?
是的
Yep.
有人杀了你？
And somebody kills you?
是的 一次又一次
Yep again.
少来 你在逗我吧
All right, come on. You're just messing with me, right?
洒水器
Sprinklers.
车鸣笛
Car alarm.
快跑
Run!
看到那些兄弟会的候选人了吗？
Now, see that pledge over there,
戴棒球帽的那个？
the one in the baseball hat?
他马上就要晕倒了…
He's going to fall right... now.
- 别停下 - 嗯
- Keep going! - Hmm.
还有问题吗？
Any questions?
薯条好吃吗？
How are your fries?
- 还不错 - 嗯
- Yeah, they're good. - Mm.
- 太让人印象深刻了 - 嗯
- That's... impressive. - Mm.
这没什么
That was nothing.
- 你都清空了吗？- 随便
- Did you get it all out? - Whatever.
反正你不会记得
You won't remember it anyway.
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone ∮
- 今天是你生日？- 耶 今天我生日
- It's your birthday? - ∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
是你爸爸 你要接吗？
It's your dad. Do you want to... want to get that?
我和我爸不亲
I was never close with my dad.
不记得上次他哪年生日打给我了
Can't even remember the last time he called me on my birthday.
总是忘记
Kind of always forgets.
我应该和他一起过生日的
Yeah. I'm supposed to be with mine.
我不知道 我不想忍受
I don't know. I couldn't bear the thought
两个人假装没事
of sitting through another uncomfortable celebration
坐在那里尴尬的庆祝
while we both pretend that everything is awesome.
你和你妈亲吗？
Are you closer with your mom?
以前亲
Was.
发生了什么？
What happened?
她…
Oh. She...
三年前
Yeah. Three years ago.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry. That...
太糟糕了
that-that sucks.
是的
Yeah.
其实我和我妈是一天生日
We actually share the same birthday, though.
真的假的？
Seriously?
难以置信
That's crazy.
我小时候
Yeah, when I was a kid,
总是逃学
I always got to skip school.
我们会去海滩
We'd go to the beach.
我爸会给我们买一块巨大的生日蛋糕
My dad would buy us this, like, huge birthday cake
上面只放一支蜡烛
and put just one candle on it.
我们俩一起吹灭它
We'd blow it out together.
我猜你一定很想她
I bet you miss her.
是的
Yeah.
说起来很好笑
You know what's funny?
你每天都在重复同一天
You relive the same day over and over again,
然后你更明白自己是谁
you kind of start to see who you really are.
如果我妈看到我现在的样子
If my mom saw me now, you know, who I've become,
我不觉得她会为我骄傲
I don't think she'd be very proud.
别这么说
Don't say that.
是真的
It's true.
我是个坏人 卡特
I'm not a good person, Carter.
也许这就是报应 我罪有应得
Maybe this is karma. Maybe I deserve it.
听着 虽然我不太了解你
Well, look, I don't... know you all that well,
但是想要改变永远不晚
but it's never too late to change.
特别是如果你说的都是真的
I mean, especially if what you're saying is true.
每一个新的日子…
Each new day is...
都有机会变成更好的人
it's a chance to be somebody better.
看 就是这样
See, that's just it.
我不觉得自己有多少机会了
I don't think I have that many chances left.
每一次回来我都变得更虚弱
I keep on getting weaker every time I come back.
也许我像猫一样只有九条命
You know, maybe I'm like that cat with nine lives.
最后我还是会死
Eventually, I'm gonna run out.
现在在贝菲尔德大学医院为您直播
Let's go live now to Bayfield University Hospital,
詹妮弗·川为您带来最新播报
where Jennifer Tran has the latest on this developing situation.
我正站在贝菲尔德大学医院的门外
I'm standing outside the Bayfield University Hospital,
杀人犯嫌疑人约翰·塘卜司因枪伤正在被救治
where suspected murderer John Tombs is being treated for a gunshot wound, following a...
能把音量调大吗？
Can you turn that up, please?
导致一名警官死亡
...that left one officer dead.
塘卜司是被全国通缉的主犯
Tombs was the subject of a nationwide manhunt that ended
- 在五个月内横跨四个州 - 怎么了？
- after a five-month pursuit across four - What's going on?
- 小翠 - 杀害了6名女性
- Tree. - state lines that left six female victims.
当局还未确认塘卜司是否…
Authorities are still not sure if Tombs is responsible
- 要为十多个被埋在 - 天啊
- for the murder of more than a dozen - Oh, my God.
亚利桑那州广袤沙漠里的被害人负责
Other victims he's claimed to have buried across the vast desert of Arizona...
他一直在这里
He's been here the whole time.
小翠 怎么了？
What? Tree!
嘿
Hey...
小翠
Tree!
他要越狱 给警察打电话
He's going to escape! Call the police!
- 谁？- 约翰·塘卜司 快报警
- Who? - John Tombs. Just call the police.
- 什么？- 别进去
- What?! - Wait, don't go in there!
该死
Shit.
请等一下 你在做什么？
Excuse me, what are you doing?
他有枪 他有枪 快跑
He has a gun! He has a gun, run!
快 快
Come on, come on.
别动
Hey!
卡特
Carter!
停下
Stop!
马上停下
Stop it right now!
嘿
Hey!
不
No.
卡特
Carter!
不
No!
小姑娘 你逃不掉的
There's nowhere to hide, little girl!
卡特
Carter.
如果我不重启今天 他会永远死去
If I don't reset this day, he's gone forever.
你本应该杀了我的
Should've killed me when you had the chance.
来吧 前进 前进 前进
Come on. Olly, olly, oxen free.
等等
Hey!
混蛋 一会儿见
See you soon, asshole.
- 哦 - 耶 今天我生日
- Oh. - ∮ It's my birthday... ∮
早 你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我昨晚不确定你
Hey, I wasn't sure if you wanted...
你竟然救了我的命
I can't believe you tried to save my life!
谢谢你
Thank you so much!
好吧
Yeah.
这没什么 我只是把你带回来了
Yeah, no biggie. I just, you know,brought you home.
不知道你还记不记得我的名字
Uh, I don't know if you remember my name.
卡特
Carter.
没错
Yeah.
你介意我借用下这个吗？
Do you mind if I borrow this?
当然不介意
Yeah, yeah. Sure.
午餐时候见
See you at lunch.
兄弟 你昨晚把那妞办了吗？
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or what?
坏小子
You naughty, naughty boy!
那个妞出门啦
Fine vagine out!
刚发生了什么？
What just happened?
- 抵制全球变暖？- 当然
- Hey. Stop global warming? - Sure.
妹子 你拯救了地球
You save that planet, girl.
洒水器快开了
Sprinklers are about to go off!
不客气
You're welcome!
大点声
I can't hear you!
噢 蒂姆
Oh, Tim!
我知道你躲在这儿
I know you're back there.
嗨 蒂姆
Hi, Tim.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
我发的短信你一条都没回
Uh, you haven't returned any of my texts.
听着 蒂姆 咱们实话实说吧
Look, Tim, let's get real.
我知道你是弯的
I know you don't like girls.
别再装了
Stop trying to be someone you're not.
真爱至上 好吗？
Love is love, right?
你赶紧滚 给自己找个男基友
Now you go out there and get yourself a fine piece of man ass.
早安
Good morning.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God.
你这个鬼鬼祟祟的小婊砸
You sneaky little beyatch.
他叫卡特
His name's Carter.
我们没上床
No, we did not have sex,
不过如果我有办法活过今天
but if I finally make it through this day somehow,
我想给他生孩子
I'm gonna have his babies.
还有事做 先走了
Lots to do, gotta go.
你可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
怎么了？
What's wrong? Ugh...
没什么
Um, nothing.
听着 洛丽
Look, Lori,
以前我是最坏的室友
I have been the worst roommate.
可你总是在我身边
You've always been there for me,
我实在是太自私了 都没有表示过感激
but I've been way too selfish to even appreciate it.
我们能重新开始吗？
Can we start over?
我保证不会再当个混蛋了
I promise not to be such a loser.
你昏头了吗？
Are you high?
我活多了
On life.
顺便说一下
Oh! By the way,
我想听听看你的神秘男孩
I want to hear about this mystery guy.
当剧烈的搅拌发生时
When extreme agitation occurs,
题目中的机能反应表现了
locomotive response in the subject shows
- 一种加速度… - 巴特勒博士
- an acceleration... - Dr. Butler.
我们能谈谈吗？
Can I have a word, please?
你干什么…
What the hell do...
你知道自己在干什么吗？
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我想结束和你的关系
I'm ending this.
等等 你说什么？
Wait, what?
我就不应该和你开始
I never should've started seeing you.
那是错的
It was wrong,
而且我…
and I...
不管怎样 过去的已经过去
Anyway, I can't change what I've done,
但从今天开始 我想重新做人
but I can start trying to be a better person today.
你励志书看多了吗？
What lame little self-help book did you get that from?
听好
You know what?
你老婆那么爱你
You have a wife who loves you so much.
如果你没办法对她忠诚
So if you can't be faithful to her,
至少勇敢地离开
at least have the balls to leave.
以后上我的课可别想水过
Don't expect me to let you coast by in my class now.
早就退班了
Already dropped it.
我想说的是
I just have to say
对于某些人在强制宿舍例会上
how totally sad and disappointing it is
缺席的情况 我感到非常失望和遗憾
when certain people can't be bothered to make it to a mandatory house meeting.
我们本该讨论今年的慈善活动
We were supposed to be picking this year's charity.
贝基？
Becky?
我是看到巧克力牛奶了吗？
Is that chocolate milk I see?
我没吃早餐
I skipped breakfast...
天啊 太好吃了
Oh, my God! That is so good.
你们要开始聚餐了吗？
What's up with the fat fest?
我们是姐妹会辣妹
We're Kappas.
别这样 亲 及时行乐
Come on, hon, live a little.
多吃点卡路里又不会死
Few calories won't kill ya.
不要
No.
我不想像贝基那样
It'll just turn me into a chunker.
满身都是肉
Like Becky here.
坐下
Okay.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
你还好吧
You'll be okay!
小翠？
Hey, Tree?
嘿
Hey.
我顺路过来…
Just, uh, coming by to...
你这是演哪一出？
What was that for?
我得走了 不过你今晚有事么？
I have to run, but what are you doing later tonight?
没事
Nothing.
能带我出去过生日吗？
Do you want to take me out for my birthday?
你不会在逗我吧？
What's the punch line?
听着 我知道这很随便
Look, I know it's really random,
但是我保证明天和你解释
but I promise I'll explain everything tomorrow.
如果有明天的话
Assuming there is one.
快说可以
Just say yes.
好吧 可以
All right. Yeah.
太棒了
Yeah.
说定了
Great.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
这杯咖啡多少钱？
Can I pay for my coffee, please?
你不吃了？
You're not gonna eat?
不吃了 请给我账单
No, just the check, please.
稍等 就来
I'll be right back.
爸爸 抱歉我来晚了
Hi, Daddy. Sorry I'm late.
我喜欢你的领带
Like your tie.
谢谢
Thanks.
校园生活怎么样？
How's school?
还不错
Fine.
喜欢你的课程吗？
Like your classes?
都挺好的 爸爸
They're fine, Dad.
我不想这样下去了
I don't want to do that anymore.
不想怎样？
Do what?
若即若离
Small talk.
只是…
It's just that...
这种日子…
this day...
今天这种日子对我来说很难熬过
this day is really... hard for me.
我想念妈妈
I miss Mom.
我很想她
You know? I miss her so much.
我想念她的气味
I miss the way that she smells.
我想念她的大笑
I miss that crazy horse laugh she has.
我也想她
Yeah. Me, too.
我以前以为
I guess I thought that if
如果我逃避这一切
I avoided all of it...
如果我逃避你
if I avoided you...
可能会容易些
that somehow it would be easier.
但事实不是这样的
But it's not.
只会变得更坏
It's been so much worse.
逃避只会让人心更凉
All of this running and hiding has made me so miserable.
我想我终于明白过来
And I think I finally figured it out.
我经历了一些傻事
For me, it took something, like, totally crazy, but...
而现在我回来了
but I'm here.
我爱你
And I love you.
很抱歉让你伤心了
And I am so, so sorry that I hurt you.
宝贝女儿 生日快乐
Happy birthday, baby.
保持冷静
Stay calm.
请慢慢站起来
I need you to stand up.
慢慢的
Slowly.
好的 非常好
Okay, good.
姑娘 你这么做可不好
Okay, this-this is a really bad idea.
死了16次也不太好
Okay, well, so is dying for the 16th time.
好了
Okay.
现在转过身来
Now turn around.
你好好听我说
I need you to listen to me.
他要逃跑了
He's going to escape.
有话好好说 把枪放下
We can talk about this. Just put the gun down.
他要逃跑了 去找人帮忙
He's going to escape. Go get help.
- 快去 - 好
- Go! - Okay.
我知道你醒着
I know you're not asleep.
睁开眼睛
Open your eyes.
保险没关 小姑娘
Safety's on, little girl.
瞧瞧这是什么？
Ah, ah, what do we have here?
你直接来找我真让我意外
You know, real nice surprise, you coming to visit me like this.
我喜欢
Whew. I like you.
好丢人
Damn shame.
你就喜欢瞎捣乱 不是吗？
But you're a feisty little shit, aingt you?
很好 爬吧 小女孩 慢慢爬
That's right. Crawl, little girl, crawl.
或者
Or...
要不要我给你个痛快？
I'll just make this one real quick for you, okay?
嘿
Hey!
保险关了
Safety's off.
多谢提醒
Thanks for the tip.
谁拿了我的吹风机？
Who took my hairdryer?
这算不算你过的最奇怪的生日？
So, this has got to be, like,the strangest birthday you've ever had, huh?
一言难尽
You have no idea.
你有想过塘卜司怎么逃出来的吗？
Did you ever figure out how Tombs got free?
不
No.
没人知道
No one knows.
好像会魔法一样
It's kind of like Houdini.
我也觉得
Yeah. I guess.
你想要什么？
What are you gonna wish for?
明天
Tomorrow.
明天？
Tomorrow?
这不是理所当然的吗？
I mean, isn't that kind of a given?
没有更高的追求了？
You want to aim for anything higher?
没了
No.
有明天就够了
Tomorrow's good enough for me.
闭嘴
Shut up!
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
赶快接电话
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone ∮
早 你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
- 卡特？- 耶 今天我生日
- Carter? - ∮ It's my birthday... ∮
是的
Yeah.
你竟然记得我名字
I'm surprised you remember my name.
昨晚你喝大了
You were pretty wasted last night.
不可能
This can't be happening.
- 怎么了？ -我明明杀了他
- What? - I killed him!
我明明杀了他
I stopped it!
谁？你在讲什么？
Who? What are you talking about?
怎么了？
What's going on?
你可能做了个噩梦
I mean, look, you were probably just having a bad dream or something.
我喝多了也这样
That happens to me all the time when I'm drinking. You know, I...
白痴 我到底在说什么
Nice one. Dickhead.
你可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
你要上哪儿去？
Going somewhere?
是的
Yes.
越远越好
As far away as possible.
小翠 怎么了？
Tree, what's wrong?
我 我错了
Me. I was wrong.
我以为只有不逃避 就可以打败它
I thought if I stopped running, that I could beat it.
但是它永远不会停下来
But it's never gonna stop!
小翠 你吓到我了
Tree, you're freaking me out.
是 我很可怕
Oh, well! That's me, a freak!
小翠
Tree...
小翠 看着
Tree, look.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
谢谢 我昨晚已经吃过了
Thanks, but I already ate it last night.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我睡觉的时候死了
I died in my sleep.
什么？
What?
你杀了我
You killed me.
什么？
What?
你下了毒
You poisoned it.
但我以前从没吃过
But I never ate it before.
所以你需要另找方法
So you had to find another way.
塘卜司刚好住进你的医院
Then Tombs fell right into your lap.
完美的替罪羊
Perfect scapegoat.
你能接近他
You had access to him.
你是先对他下的毒吗？
Did you drug him first?
你觉得如果他逃跑了
You knew that if he escaped,
大家都会以为我是他杀的
everyone would assume that he killed me.
其实一直都是你
But it was always you.
小翠 你在开玩笑吗？
Tree, are... is this a joke?
你真以为我会用一个纸杯蛋糕毒杀你？
You think I would actually try to poison you with a freaking cupcake?
好吧
Okay, then.
证明一下
Prove it.
吃吧 洛丽
Go on, Lori.
咬一口
Take a bite.
吃呀 洛丽
Go on, Lori.
你真的疯了
You really are crazy.
好吧
Okay, then.
我会把它带到警察那去
I'll take it down to the police.
我相信他们会告诉我
I'm sure they can tell us
你的小蛋糕里有什么
what your little birthday treat is made of.
你个小贱人
You stupid little whore.
我知道我不是好室友
I know I've been a bad roommate,
但这是不是有点过了？
but isn't this a bit much?
搞什么？
What the hell?!
我也不知道啊
Oh, I don't know,
可能是因为你一直跟他睡觉吧
maybe because you wouldn't stop sleeping with him.
什么？
What?
格里高利？
Gregory?
他选了你
But he just kept choosing you.
而不是我
Over me.
他就是喜欢你这种贱货
Guess all he wanted was a cheap slut like you!
等等
Wait.
你为了个蠢男人杀了我？
You've been killing me over some stupid guy?
不只是因为这个
Oh, that's not the only reason.
还因为你是个贱人
You're a dumb bitch, too!
我想知道的是…
But what I really want to know is...
你是怎么发现的？
...how did you figure it out?
因为你已经杀过我了
Because you've killed me before.
那我只能再杀你一次了
Then I guess I'm just gonna have to do it again.
住手 婊子
No! Bitch!
不
No!
发生什么事了？
What the hell is going on in there?
没事
Nothing.
小翠刚才摔倒了
Tree just fell.
不用担心
Everything's fine.
随你吧 小蠢货
Whatever. Clumsy hoes.
一会儿开会见
I better see you at the meeting today.
一会儿见
We'll be there.
吃吧 婊子
Eat it, bitch!
你们到底在做什么？
What are you losers doing in there?
洛丽
Lori...
吃了
ate...
我的纸杯蛋糕
my cupcake.
我就知道洛丽有问题
I just knew there was something wrong with Lori.
她从不化妆
She never wore makeup,
也不发自拍
never posted any cute selfies,
她竟然还穿凉拖鞋
and she literally owned a pair of Crocs.
所有迹象都表明她是个变态杀人狂…
All the signs of a psycho killer were th...
可以小点声吗？
Hello?
没看见我在接受采访吗？
I'm trying to get interviewed here.
我的天啊 她真是个人才
Oh, my God, she is such a tool.
不管怎样 洛丽的杀人计划太傻了
Anyhoo... Lori's little plot was super lame.
用纸杯蛋糕杀人？想什么呢？
Poisoning a cupcake? Really?
我们是姐妹会辣妹
We're Kappas.
我们不吃纸杯蛋糕
We don't eat cupcakes.
- 你们是地方台还是国际台？- 耶 今天我生日
- Is this local or national? - ∮ It's my birthday ∮
- 地方台 - 赶快接电话
- Local. - ∮ And I ain't gotta... ∮
- 小翠 亲爱的 你还好吗？- 嗨 爸爸
- Tree, honey, are you okay? - Hey, Dad.
- 爸 - 你受伤了吗？
- Dad. - Are you hurt?
爸 没有 我没事
Dad, no, Dad, I'm fine.
我保证
I promise.
- 你确定吗？- 是的
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
只是有点混乱
I'm just a little scratched up.
好吧
All right.
一会儿见
Okay. I'll see you soon.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你 拜
- I love you. - I love you, too. Bye.
现在你卧室成杀人现场了
So, uh, now that your... bedroom is officially a crime scene and all,
今晚想去哪儿？
uh, where you planning on crashing tonight?
你在邀请我吗？
Is that an invitation?
你不会还想在宿舍醒来吧？
You sure you want to wake up in a dorm room again?
是你的就没问题
Only if it's yours.
我意思是
Well, I mean, of course,
你得睡瑞恩床上了
you'll have to sleep in Ryan's bed.
- 没问题 - 好的
- Of course. - Yeah.
我们可以
We can, yeah...
差点忘了
almost forgot.
你忘了这个
You left this little guy.
谢谢
Thanks.
知道你的故事让我想到什么了吗？
You know what your little scenario reminds me of?
什么？
What?
- 呃… - 快说
- Uh... - What's that?
《土拨鼠之日》
Groundhog Day.
《土拨鼠之日》那部电影？
The movie, Groundhog Day?
我没看过
I don't know.
比尔·莫瑞演的？
With Bill Murray?
比尔·莫瑞是谁？
Who's Bill Murray?
你难道没看过《捉鬼敢死队》吗？
Are you kidding me? Ghostbusters.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 我没看过 - 你昨晚睡得好吗？
- I don't know. - How do you sleep at night?
- 你从来没看过《土拨鼠之日》？- 没有
- You've never seen Groundhog Day? - No.
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday ∮
- 哦 嘿 - 赶快接电话
- Oh, hey. - ∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone ∮
你醒了
You're up.
耶 今天我生日
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday... ∮
我昨晚不确定你是否想睡这儿
I wasn't sure if you wanted to, uh, you know,sleep in or not.
噢 天啊
Oh, my...
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
是… 是我
It was, it was me.
我刚给你打的电话
I just called your phone.
什么？
What?
今天是星期二 19号
It's Tuesday the 19th.
你做到了
You made it.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
你吓死我了
You are such a jerk!
- 我要杀了你 - 好了 够了
- I'm gonna kill you! - Hey. That's not...
- 你怎么回事？- 嘿 嘿 嘿
- What is wrong with you? - H-Hey, hey. Hey.
那根本不好笑
That was not funny!
你的笑话很低级
You are such a punk!
我讨厌你
I hate you.
- 她回来了？- 出去
- She's back? - Out.
我才不想再去车里睡
I'm not sleeping in my car again.
闻起来像热三明治和脚臭
It smells like Hot Pockets and feet.
快出去
Get out.
我就换条内裤
I just want clean underwear!
清静了
Yeah.
(今天是你余生第一天)
《忌日快乐》